TUTUSFX COMPLAINTS PROCEDURE FOR CLIENTS

Last updated June 2 6 th , 201 9

We, Tutusfx Group (hereinafter, the “ Group ”), have adopted this Complaints Procedure in order to ensure a fair and quick process for handling complaints that may arise from our relationship.

The Group owns and regulates the brand , Tutusfx .

1. Submitting your Complaint

In order to submit a complaint to the Group , you are kindly requested to complete and submit the Complaint Form of the Group (click the button below). Please note that the Group may not accept complaints submitted to it by any other mean s /method s (i.e. e-mail, telephone, etc.).

Click Here to proceed to the Complaint Form

Once you successfully complete and submit your complaint, the relevant Department of the Group shall handle and investigate your complaint.

2. Acknowledging your Complaint

We will acknowledge receipt of your complaint within five (5) days from the receipt of your complaint and provide you the Reference ID of your complaint. The Reference ID should be used in all your future contact with the Group , a nd/or any of the Group’s affiliate bodies, regarding the specific complaint.

3. Handling of your Complaint

Once we acknowledge receipt of your complaint we will review it carefully, investigate the circumstances surrounding your complaint and will try to resolve it without undue delay. We shall make every effort to investigate your complaint and provide you with the outcome of our investigation within 6 0 day s from the date you have submitted your complaint to us. During the investigation process will keep you updated of the handling process of your complaint. One of our officers may contact you directly (including communication by email or phone) in order to obtain, where needed, further clarifications and information relating to your complaint. We will require your full cooperation in order to expedite the investigation and possible resolution of your complaint.

Tutusfx Group

1

-----------------------------------------------------Page 1-----------------------------------------------------
﻿
In the event that your complaint requires further investigation and we cannot resolve it within two (2) months, we will issue a holding response in writing or other durable medium. When a holding response is sent, it will indicate the causes of the delay and when the Group ’s investigation is likely to be completed. In any event, we shall provide you with the outcome of our investigation no later than one (1) month from the issuing of the holding response, depending on the complexity of the case and your cooperation. Please note that the Group shall consider your complaint as closed and cease the relevant investigation in case you fail to respond to our officers within the period of three (3) months from the date of the submission of your complaint. When we reach an outcome we will inform you of it together with an explanation of our position and any remedy measures we intend to take (if applicable).

4.    Final Decision

When we reach an outcome we will inform you of it together with an explanation of our position and any remedy measures we intend to take (if applicable).

It is understood that your right to take legal action remains unaffected by the existence or use of any complaints procedures referred to above.

Tutusfx Group

2

-----------------------------------------------------Page 2-----------------------------------------------------
